邪恶力量前情提要
Previously on Supernatural.
萨姆
Sammy.
赶快带你弟弟离开屋子 快
Take your brother outside as fast as you can. Go!
爸爸已经踏上了捕猎之旅 他好几天没回家了
Dad's on a hunting trip. And he hasn't been home in a few days.
这是老爸最珍贵的财产
This is Dad's book.
他了解的有关恶魔的一切都记载在这里面
I think he wants us to pick up where he left off.
救助他人 猎杀恶魔 家族事业
Saving people, hunting things. The family business.
你认为妈妈愿意我们这么做吗
Think Mom would've wanted this?
- 我一个人无法完成 - 我来开
- Can't do this alone. - I'm driving.
《邪恶力量》
（俄克拉荷马州 绿洲平原）
这些房子很不错 是吧
Man, these are some phat houses, huh?
我希望能住在这里
I'd like to live here.
是啊 可惜的是你负担不起
Yeah. Too bad you can't afford it.
是啊
Yeah, you're right.
当这里修好了后 周围的房价也会特别高
This neighborhood will be damn expensive when it's done.
这地方太完美了
This place is perfect.
就这蚊子讨厌点
Except for the mosquitoes.
达斯汀
Dustin?
快来救我 我掉下去了 我摔断了我的腿
Help me. l'm trapped! I broke my ankle!
我去拿绳子
All right, l'll get a rope.
该死
Oh, damn.
哦 天啊
Oh, God.
- 特拉维斯 快来救我 - 坚持住
- Travis! Help! - Hang on!
特拉维斯 救我 啊
Travis, help!
没事的 达斯汀 没事的
It's okay, Dustin, it's okay.
达斯汀 我在这里 我的天啊
Dustin? Dustin, I'm here. Oh, God.
其实我们白天可以找份工作的
You know, we could get day jobs once in a while.
猎杀魔鬼才是我们的工作 但工资却是赌金
Hunting's our day job. And the pay is crap.
所以就去赌博 盗用信用卡吗
Yeah, but hustling pool?Credit card scams?
这可不是正经人该做的事
Not the most honest thing in the world, Dean.
这听上还有点意思
Well, let's see. Honest fun and easy.
但这根本没必要讨论
It's no contest.
而且我们干的也不错
Besides, we're good at it.
我们从小就被这样教育
It's what we were raised to do.
我们被教会的只是欺骗
Well, how we were raised was jacked.
随便你怎么说
Yeah, says you.
- 我们有了新状况 - 可能
- We got a new gig or what? - Maybe.
俄克拉荷马州离这里不远
Oasis Plains, Oklahoma. Not far from here.
瓦斯公司的雇员
A gas-company employee.
达斯汀·柏华斯突然死于疯牛病
Dustin Burwash supposedly died from Creutzfeldt-Jakob.
人类疯牛病
Human mad cow disease.
疯牛病
Mad cow.
这个没上脱口秀节目吗
Wasn't that on Oorah?
你也看脱口秀
You watch Oorah?
看来这个家伙吃了有病的汉堡包
So this guy eats a bad burger.
怎么是我们的问题呢
Why is it our kind of thing?
疯牛病导致脑部细胞的大量恶化
Mad cow disease causes massive brain degeneration.
不过需要数个月 甚至几年才会出现症状
It takes months, even years, for the damage to appear.
但这个家伙达斯汀
But this guy Dustin.
他的脑子象在一个小时内就破坏了
sounds like his brain disintegrated in about an hour.
也许时间更短
Maybe less.
这很奇怪
Okay. That's weird.
它也可能是种疾病
Yeah. Now, it could be a disease.
也可能是某些鬼怪
Or it could be something much nastier.
好吧 去俄克拉荷马州
All right. Oklahoma.
伙计们 加油
Man. Work, work, work.
没时间享受了
No time to spend my money.
特拉维斯·韦弗
Travis Weaver?
是我
Yeah, that's right.
你就是和叔叔达斯汀 一起工作的特拉维斯吗
Are you the Travis who worked with Uncle Dusty?
达斯汀从没提起有个侄子
Dustin never mentioned nephews.
真的吗 他可是有提到过你的哦
Really? Well, he sure mentioned you.
他说你是最棒的
He said you were the greatest.
是吗 呵呵
Yeah. Oh, he did?
我们想问问你 当时到底发生了什么
Listen, we wanted to ask you, what exactly happened out there?
我也不确定 他跌进了污水池
I'm not sure.He fell in a sinkhole.
我跑到卡车那拿些绳子
I went to the truck to get some rope…
可在我回来前…
and by the time I got back…
你看到什么
What did you see?
没什么 只有Dustin
Nothing. Just Dustin.
没有伤痕或其它什么的
No wounds or anything?
他的眼睛耳朵和鼻子都在流血 就是那样
Well, he was bleeding from his eyes and his ears, his nose. That's it.
你觉得这是疯牛病吗
So you think it could be this whole mad cow thing?
我不知道
I don't know.
医生是那么诊断的
That's what the doctors are saying.
可如果是疯牛病 他之前一定有奇怪的行为
But if it was, he would've acted strange beforehand…
比如痴呆 情绪失控
like dementia, loss of motor control.
你之前注意到他有这样过吗
You ever notice anything like that?
没有
No. No way.
如果那不是病 那是什么呢
But then if it wasn't some disease, what the hell was it?
问的好
That's a good question.
你能告诉我们这是在哪里发生的吗
Can you tell us where this happened?
可以
Yeah.
你怎么认为
Huh. What do you think?
我不太清楚 但如果特拉维斯说的是真的
I don't know. But if Travis was right.
这也发生的太快了
it happened pretty damn fast.
那又怎么样
So, what.
某种生物吞噬他的脑部吗
some sort of creature chewed on his brain?
但没有这样的伤口
No, there'd be an entry wound.
听起来象伤害是在这里面造成的
Sounds like this thing worked from the inside.
看起来只能一个人下去
Looks like there's only room for one.
掷硬币解决
You wanna flip a coin?
迪恩 我们不知道那下面有什么
Dean, we have no idea what's down there.
如果你害怕的话 我去好了
All right. l'll go if you're scared.
- 害怕吗 - 来 掷硬币解决
- Scared? - Flip the damn coin.
来吧 小子
All right, call it in the air, chicken.
我去
l'm going.
我说我去的
l said l'd go.
我要去
l'm going.
好吧
All right.
别把我扔下去啊
Don't drop me.
你在那个洞里找到了些甲虫
So you found some beetles. ln a hole in the ground.
这让我觉得奇怪 Sam
That's shocking, Sam.
那里没有地道 没有通道
There were no tunnels, no tracks no evidence.
在那里没有任何生物的迹象
of any other kind of creature down there.
但你要知道 有些甲虫吃肉的 通常是死人肉
You know, some beetles do eat meat. It's usually dead meat, but.
你在那里找到了多少只虫
How many did you find down there?
10个
Ten.
但要吞噬掉人的脑子 可需要到更多的虫
It'd take more than that to eat out some dude's brain.
也许当时有很多
Well, maybe there were more.
我也不清楚
I don't know.
听起来要慢慢解决了
Sounds like a stretch to me.
我们需要关于这个地区更多的资料 例如信息 街道
We need more information on the area the neighborhood.
还有是否有类似的事情发生
whether something like this has ever happened before.
什么
What?
我知道有个好地方下手了
l know a good place to start.
那有个烤肉聚会 怎么样
I'm kind of hungry for a little barbecue, how about you?
我们可以和当地的人谈谈
We can't talk to the locals?
你不是想去吃白食吧
The free food's got nothing to do with it?
当然不是
Of course not.
我很敬业的
I'm a professional.
好吧
Right.
在这样的环境长大我会疯掉
Growing up in a place like this would freak me out.
为什么
Why?
看看这修剪过的草地 天天重复的打招呼
The manicured lawns, "How was your day, honey?"
我想这会让我疯掉的
I'd blow my brains out.
平凡的日子并没有错
There's nothing wrong with normal.
我在家可过的不平凡
I'd take our family over normal any day.
欢迎你们
Welcome.
有烤肉聚会吗
ls this the barbecue?
是的 但天气是不太好
Yeah. Not the best weather, but…
我是 拉里派克 这里的开发商 你们是
I'm Larry Pike, the developer here.And you are…?
迪恩 这是 萨姆
Dean. This is Sam.
萨姆 迪恩 很高兴认识你们
Sam, Dean. Good to meet you.
你们对这些房子有兴趣吗
So you're interested in Oasis Plains?
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
其实我们接受任何种族 信仰 肤色
Let me just say, we accept homeowners of any race, religion, color.
或性取向的
or sexual orientation.
我们是兄弟
We're brothers.
我们的父亲上了年纪了 我们想给他买套房子
Our father's getting on in years. We're looking for a place for him.
这很好
Great. Great.
老人也欢迎啊 进来
Well, seniors are welcome too.
来吧
Come on in.
真是难以置信的
This is fabulous.
你说你是开发商
You said you were the developer?
18个月前我和我的调查组考察了这个峡谷
Eighteen months ago, I was walking this valley with my survey team.
这里除了丛林和松鼠外什么都没有
There was nothing here but scrub brush and squirrels.
我们修建了一个如此美丽适合居住的地方
You know what, we built such a nice place to live.
我自己也来到这定居
That I actually bought into it myself.
这就是我们的家
This is our house.
我们是第一户家庭
We're the first family in Oasis Plains.
这是我老婆 乔安妮
This is my wife, Joanie.
你好
ere. Hi.
嗨 很高兴认识你
Hi, nice to meet you.
- 迪恩 - 萨姆
- Dean. - Sam.
告诉他们你有多喜欢这个地方 亲爱的
Tell them how much you love the place, honey.
- 如果需要你也撒点谎 因为我也需要卖掉房子 - 好的
And lie if you have to… - because I need to sell some houses. - Right.
孩子们 失陪一下了
Boys, if you'll excuse me.
别让他的商人本色吓到了你门
Don't let his salesman routine scare you.
但这是一个很值得居住的地方
This really is a great place to live.
嗨 我是琳达·布鲁姆 销售经理
Hi, I'm Lynda Bloome, head of sales.
琳达 是第2家搬进来住的
Lynda was second to move in.
可是她真是个很吵的邻居
She's a very noisy neighbor, though.
她在开玩笑
She's kidding, of course.
我想你两很有兴趣成为业主吧
I take it you two are interested in becoming homeowners?
- 嗯 - 是的
- Well… - Yeah, well.
其实我们接受任何种族 信仰 肤色
Let me just say that we accept homeowners of any race, religion, color.
或性取向的
or sexual orientation.
嗯
Right.
好的
Yeah.
嗯 我去和拉里谈谈
I'm gonna go talk to Larry.
好吗 亲爱的
Okay, honey?
你有三种选择 地毯 硬木地板和瓷砖
You got three choices Carpet, hardwood and tile.
哇 有人喜欢虫子
Oh. Someone likes bugs.
我的儿子 他沉迷于此
My son. He's into insects.
他对这个很好奇
He's very inquisitive.
谁能抗拒蒸汽浴室呢
Hmm. Who can say no to a steam shower?
我每天都得用它
I use mine every day.
听起来很不错
Sounds great.
你有三种浴缸可以选择的
You also have three different whirlpool tubs to choose from.
浴缸的器件是用镍和铜做的
The hardware for the tubs includes nickel or brass.
当你去到厨房的时候…
In the kitchen you can choose.
不好意思
Excuse me.
没关系
Okay.
这是你的吗
Is this yours?
你会告诉我爸吗
You gonna tell my dad?
我不知道
l don't know.
谁是你爸爸
Who's your dad?
哦 拉里通常在家庭介绍的时候都会忽略我
Yeah. Larry usually skips me in the family introductions.
这样直呼你父亲 好象不太好啊
Ouch. The first-name basis with the old man sounds pretty grim.
我可不是什么宣传材料
Well, l'm not exactly brochure material.
不要那样 会好转的 我发誓
Well, hang in there. It gets better, I promise.
马修
Matthew.
我为我的儿子和他的宠物道歉
I am so sorry about my son and his pet.
没关系
It's no bother.
对不起
Excuse us.
让你想起某人了吧
Remind you of somebody?
老爸
Dad?
老爸从没对我们那样
Dad never treated us like that.
是老爸没对你那样吧
Well, Dad never treated you like that.
你太完美了 他总是在责怪我
You were perfect. He was all over my case.
你不记得了吗
You don't remember?
也许有的时候他凶了点 但有的时候是你过分了点
Maybe he had to raise his voice, but sometimes you were out of line.
是啊 就像我说我宁愿去踢球 也不想学打猎
Right. Like when I said I'd rather play soccer than learn bowhunting.
但打猎是个很重要的技能啊
Bowhunting's an important skill.
别说了 你那边怎么样
Whatever.How was your tour?
很棒 我想买了
Oh, it was excellent. I'm ready to buy.
你发现了点什么吧
So you might be on to something.
看起来达斯汀·柏华斯不是在这的第一起离奇死亡事件
Looks like Dustin Burwash wasn't the first strange death here.
发生了什么
What happened?
大概一年前 在他们破土动工前
A year ago, before they broke ground…
拉里的调查小组中一员在工作的时候摔死了
one of Larry's surveyors dropped dead on the job.
说是死于蜂螫后的剧烈过敏
Get this a severe allergic reaction to bee stings.
- 应该是虫子干的 - 是的
- More bugs. - More bugs.
我听过杀人蜂 可是杀人甲虫
I've heard of killer bees, but killer beetles?
是什么让不同的昆虫来袭击呢
What is it that could make different bugs attack?
有的时候虫子会聚集起来
Well, hauntings sometimes include bug manifestations.
可我没发现鬼魂的迹象
But I didn't see any evidence of ghost activity.
我也是这样认为
Yeah, me neither.
也许他们被控制了 被某人或某样东西
Maybe they're being controlled somehow. You know, by something or someone.
你指就象
You mean like Willard?
只是虫子代替了老鼠而已
Yeah. Bugs instead of rats.
有好多人与动物精神联接的例子
There are cases of psychic connections between people and animals.
例如心灵感应
Elementals, telepaths.
还有一些灵异事件
Yeah, the whole TimmyLassie thing.
拉里的儿子 他把虫子当成宠物养
Larry's kid. Bugs for pets.
- 马特 - 嗯
- Matt? - Yeah.
他想用一只狼蛛吓唬那个房产经济人
He tried to scare the realtor with a tarantula.
你认为他就是我们要找的 吗
Think he's our Willard?
我不知道
l don't know.
我觉得什么都有可能
Anything's possible, I guess.
在这里停一下
Hey, pull over here.
我们在这里干吗
What are we doing here?
现在没法子再通知别人了
It's too late to talk to anybody else.
我们要呆在这个空房子里面吗
We're gonna squat in an empty house?
我想试试这里的蒸汽浴室 来吧
I wanna try the steam shower. Come on.
来啊
Come on!
阿托卡县今天开始在此区域
Atoka Valley County began mandatory insecticide spraying across.
强制碰洒杀虫剂
a wide swath of the district today.
官方说作出喷杀决定是因为
Authorities say the decision to spray was.
伴随着某些区域内蚊虫的数量的大增
made because of several recent cases of West Nile virus.
出现了几起乃尔病毒的病例
coupled with a dramatic increase in the mosquito population in some areas.
虽然有些本地居民担心如此高浓度的
Although some residents cite concerns about the high.
杀虫剂的使用
levels of pesticide.
你还没出来吗 迪恩
You ever coming out of there?
什么
What?
迪恩 有警察打电话进来了
A police call came in on the scanner.
等等
Hold on.
有人发现老爸就在三条街外 来吧
Someone was found dead three blocks from here. Come on.
这个淋浴太爽了
This shower is awesome.
来吧
Come on!
好的 我现在也不知道到底是怎么回事
Look, I don't know anything more right now.
我会再打给你
I'll have to call you back.
好的
All right.
好啊 你们来的好早啊
Hello. You're back early.
我们想看看新的邻居
We just drove in to take another look at the neighborhood.
发生什么啦
What's going on?
你们在烤饶聚会上遇到过 Linda Bloom
You guys met Lynda Bloome at the barbecue?
那个经济人吧
The realtor.
她昨天晚上死了
Well, she passed away last night.
发生了什么
What happened?
我也想找出原因
I'm still trying to find out.
我让警察在检查尸体
I identified the body for the police.
对不起 现在真的很糟糕
Look, l'm sorry. This isn't a good time.
没事
It's okay.
对不起
Excuse me.
你知道我们要怎么做了吧
You know what we have to do, right?
我们得到那个房子里去
Yeah. Get in that house.
看是不是虫子的问题
See if we got a bug problem.
看来就是这里
This looks like the place.
蜘蛛 那个喜欢蜘蛛的孩子吗
Spiders. From Spider-Boy?
马特 也许
Matt. Maybe.
他家是这条路吗
Isn't his house that way?
嗯
Yep.
他去哪
So where's he going?
马特 还记得我吗
Hey, Matt. Remember me?
你们在这里干吗
What are you doing out here?
我们想和你谈谈
Well, we wanna talk to you.
你们来这不是想买房子吧 是吗
You're not here to buy a house, are you?
等等 你们不是这一系列的杀手吧
Wait. You're not serial killers?
不是 我想你很安全
No, no. No, I think you're safe.
马特 你知道很多关于虫子的东西
So, Matt…you sure know a lot about insects.
那又怎样
So?
你听到发生在经济人 琳达 身上的事吗
Did you hear what happened to Lynda, the realtor?
我今早听说她死了
l hear she died this morning.
对的 蜘蛛咬的
That's right. Spider bites.
马特 你想用蜘蛛吓她
Matt, you tried to scare her with a spider.
等等 你们认为我和这个有关系吗
Wait. You think I had something to do with that?
你告诉我们吧
You tell us.
那个狼蛛只是个玩笑
That tarantula was a joke.
而且这也不能解释 蜜蜂攻击和燃气公司的职员的事情
Anyway, that wouldn't explain the bee attack or the gas-company guy.
你也知道那些
You know about those?
这里有些事情在进行
There is something going on here.
我不清楚 可我知道和虫子有关系
I don't know what, but something's happening with the insects.
让我带你去看看
Let me show you something.
你知道了这些有关于虫子为什么不告诉你爸
So if you knew about all this bug stuff, why not tell your dad?
他也许能让所有人离开
Maybe he could clear everybody out.
相信我 我试过了但是Larry不听我的
Believe me, l've tried…but Larry doesn't listen to me.
为什么不
Why not?
总而言之 他对他这个怪儿子很失望
Mostly? He's too disappointed in his freak son.
- 我知道 - 这你也知道
- I hear you. - You do?
马特 你多大了
Matt, how old are you?
16岁了
Sixteen.
别太气愤了 两年后就还有更大事要发生
Don't sweat it, because in two years, something great's gonna happen.
什么
What?
上大学
College.
你会离开这个家 离开你的爸爸
You'll be able to get out of that house and away from your dad.
这是什么建议啊 一个小孩应该呆在他家里
What kind of advice is that? Kid should stick with his family.
还要走多久 马特
How much further.
我们很接近了
Matt? We're close.
我在追踪虫子的数量的痕迹
I've been keeping track of insect populations.
这是选修科学班的一部分作业
It's part of an AP science class.
你两还真像啊
You two are like peas in a pod.
发生什么事了
What's been happening?
有许多
A lot.
从蜜蜂到蚯蚓 甲虫
I mean, from bees to earthworms, beetles…
随你叫的出的名字
you name it.
看上去它们就在这里聚集
It's like they're congregating here.
为什么
Why?
我不知道
l don't know.
那是什么
What's that?
下面有东西
There's something down there.
来吧 来吧
Come on. Come on.
无名墓地下的一堆尸骨
So a bunch of skeletons in an unmarked grave.
也许这就是聚集的原因
Well, maybe this is a haunting. Pissed-off spirits…
某些愤怒的灵魂 还有它没完成的心愿
some unfinished business?
是的
Yeah, maybe.
问题是为什么是虫子而且是在现在
The question is, why bugs? And why now?
那是两个问题
That's two questions.
回到那个男孩的问题
Hey, so with that kid back there…
你怎么能教他和家里划清界限呢
how could you tell him to just ditch his family like that?
只是我知道那个男孩现在处于什么状况
Just, I know what the kid's going through.
告诉他尊敬他的老爸不好吗
How about telling him to respect his old man?
这个建议怎么样
How's that for advice?
迪恩 拜托
Dean, come on.
这和他爸爸无关
This isn't about his old man.
你觉得我不尊敬爸爸
You think I didn't respect Dad.
这就是你想说的
That's what this is about.
请忘记它 我很抱歉我那么说
Let's forget it. Sorry I brought it up.
我尊敬他 可无论我怎么做 他都觉得不够好
l respected him. But no matter what I did, it was never good enough.
你是什么意思 你觉得老爸过去对你很失望
So, what, Dad was disappointed in you? "Was"?
无论是过去还是现在都一样
ls. Always has been.
你为什么会那么想
Why would you think that?
因为我不想用弓去猎杀或是去骗傻子
Because I didn't wanna bowhunt. Or hustle pool.
因为我想去上学 去过我自己的生活
Because I wanted to go to school and live my life.
这却在让我在这家庭里成为了怪人
Which, in our whacked-out family, made me the freak.
你就像是在怪兽家族里的小鸡
Yeah, you were kind of like the blond chick in The Munsters.
迪恩 当一个孩子拿了满分后 大部分父亲会怎么做
Dean, you know what most dads are when their kids score a full ride?
骄傲 他们绝不会把他的孩子赶出家门
Proud. Most dads don't toss their kids out of the house.
我记得那场争吵
I remember that fight.
事实上 我看来唤起了你的一些片段
In fact, I seem to recall a few choice phrases coming out of your mouth.
你知道吗 事实是当我们最后找到了父亲
You know, truth is, when we finally do find Dad.
我都不知道他是否想见我
l don't know if he's even gonna wanna see me.
萨姆父亲从来没有对你失望过
Sam, Dad was never disappointed in you.
从来没有
Never.
他很害怕
He was scared.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
他害怕如果他不在你身边 会有些事情发生在你身上
He was afraid of what could've happened to you if he wasn't around.
即使当你们在不说话的冷战期
But even when you two weren't talking…
他都尽可能的呆在斯坦福那里
he used to swing by Stanford whenever he could.
看着你 确定你很安全
Keep an eye on you. Make sure you were safe.
是真的吗
What?
是的
Yeah.
他为什么不告诉我
Why didn't he tell me any of that?
那得看双方的意愿 兄弟
Well, it's a two-way street, dude.
那时你应该接电话的
You could have picked up the phone.
来吧 我们约会要迟到了
Come on. We're gonna be late for our appointment.
你们是学生
So you two are students?
是的
Yeah. Yeah.
我们是你班上的
We're in your class.
课程代号101
Anthro 1 01?
哦
Oh, yeah.
这骨头有什么 教授
So, what about the bones, professor?
你们找到一件很有趣的东西
This is quite an interesting find you've made.
我说他有差不多170岁了
I'd say they're 1 70 years old, give or take.
从时间历史和地理学 能充分证明这是土著人
The time frame and the geography heavily suggest Native American.
那个时候这片土地上有这样的部落吗
Were there any tribes or reservations on that land?
历史记录上没有记载
Not according to the historical record.
但是土著人的迁徙那个时候很普遍
But the relocation of native peoples was quite common at that time.
那好吧 那有没有些当地的传说 关于这个地方的
Right. Well, are there any local legends? Oral histories about the area?
这里有个部落在萨帕尔帕
Well you know, there's a Euchee tribe in Sapulpa.
离这里大概60公里
It's about 60 miles from here.
在那里的某人可能知道真相
Someone out there might know the truth.
好的
All right.
乔·怀特
Joe White Tree?
如果允许的话 我们想问你几个问题
We'd like to ask you a few questions, if that's all right.
我们是大学生
We're students from the university.
你们不是 你在撒谎
No, you're not. You're lying.
那好吧 事实是
Um… Well, truth is.
你是骗子却用事这句话做为自己的开场白的吗
You know who starts sentence with "truth is"? Liars.
你知道那些
Have you heard of Oasis Plains?
那些靠近阿托卡的住宅区吗
It's a housing development near the Atoka Valley.
我喜欢他 他没撒谎
I like him. He's not a liar.
我知道那个地方
I know the area.
你能告诉我有关那里的历史吗
What can you tell us about the history there?
你们为什么想知道
Why do you wanna know?
某些事情 某些不好的事在绿洲平原那里发生
Something…Something bad is happening in Oasis Plains.
我想它和我们在那里发现的 某些古老的尸骨有关
We think it might have something to do with some old bones we found there.
土著人的尸骨
Native American bones.
我会告诉你 我祖父告诉我的事
I'll tell you what my grandfather told me.
而那是他祖父告诉他的
What his grandfather told him.
200 年前 我的祖先居住在那个峡谷
Two hundred years ago, a band of my ancestors lived in that valley.
一天美国的殖民者来让他们迁走
One day the American cavalry came to relocate them.
他们抵抗了 殖民者没了耐性
They were resistant…the cavalry impatient.
我祖父说的
As my grandfather put it.
在晚上 月亮和太阳占的天空是一样
"On the night the moon and the sun share the sky as equals…
一天殖民者开始袭击村落
the cavalry first raided our village."
他们烧杀 掳掠
They murdered, raped.
第二天他们又来了
The next day, the cavalry came again.
一天接一天直到第六天的晚上
And the next and the next.And on the sixth night.
殖民者来的最后一次
the cavalry came one last time.
在天亮前那刻所有在村落的
And by the time the sun rose…
男人 女人 小孩都死了
every man, woman and child still in the village was dead.
他们说在第六日的晚上
They say on the sixth night…
村落的首领在死去时
as the chief of the village lay dying…
他对天低吟
he whispered to the heavens…
再没有白人能侵占这片土地
that no white man would ever tarnish this land again.
自然会来保护这个峡谷
Nature would rise up and protect the valley.
这会让殖民者给他的人民带来
And it would bring as many days of misery and death.
同样的悲惨和死亡
to the white man as the cavalry had brought upon his people.
虫子 这就是自然
Insects. Sounds like nature to me.
- 那六天呢 - 在第六天的晚上 没人能活下来
- Six days. - And on the night of the sixth day…none would survive.
那个燃气公司的雇员什么时候死的
When did the gascompany man die? Uh…
我们来这是星期二 20 号是星期五
Let's see. We got here Tuesday, so Friday the 20th.
5月20号 那是春分
rch 20th. That's the spring equinox.
太阳和月亮占的天空是一样的
The night the sun and the moon share the sky as equals.
所以每年的这个时候 这里都会有危险
So every year about this time, anybody in Oasis Plains is in danger.
拉里的房子修在了被诅咒的地方
Larry built his neighborhood on cursed land.
第六个晚上 那就是今晚
On the sixth night, that's tonight.
如果我们不做些什么 拉里一家会在天亮前死去
If we don't do something, Larry's family will be dead by sunrise.
我们怎么打破诅咒呢
So how do we break a curse?
你不必打破它
You don't break a curse.
你离开它 我们要把那些人带走
You get out of its way. We gotta get those people out now.
是的 派克先生 在你的隔壁有很严重的煤气泄露
Yes, Mr. Pike. There's a mainline gas leak in your neighborhood.
天啊 真的吗 多严重
God. Really? How big?
现在扩张的很大了
Fairly extensive.
我不想吓唬你 但
I don't wanna alarm you. but.
我们需要你在 2小时内撤离 为了安全
we need your family out of the vicinity for at least 12 hours.
再问一下 你是谁
Just to be safe. Who is this again?
特拉维斯·韦弗
Travis Weaver.
我为俄克拉荷马州燃气能源公司工作
I work for Oklahoma Gas and Power.
哦
Uh-huh.
问题是我认识特拉维斯
TravisThe problem is, I know Travis.
我们一起工作了一年
He's worked with us for a year.
你是谁
So who is this?
嗯
Uh…
给我电话
Give me the phone.
你好
Hello?
马特 我是萨姆
Matt, it's Sam.
萨姆 后园里有很多蟑螂
Sam, My back yard's crawling with cockroaches.
马特 听我说
Matt, just listen.
你必须马上带你全家离开那里 听到吗
You have to get your family out of that house now.
为什么
What? Why?
因为有东西会出现
Because something's coming.
很多虫子
More bugs.
是的 很多很多
Yeah. A lot more.
最好的情形下 爸爸都不会听我的
My dad doesn't listen in the best of circumstances.
更何况现在是半夜11点半了 我该怎么说
What am I supposed to tell him?
你要让他相信你 好吗
You gotta make him listen.
给我电话
Give me the phone.
马特 无论在那种情形下你说出事实
Under no circumstances are you to tell the truth.
他都会认为你在说胡话
He'll think you're nuts.
但他是我的…
But, he's my.
告诉他你现在很疼
Say you have a sharp pain in your right.
你想要去医院 好吗
side and you gotta go to the hospital. Ok?
好的 好的
Yeah. Yeah, okay.
让他听我的
"Make him listen."
你在想什么
What are you thinking?
天那 他们还在这 来吧
Damn it. They're still here. Come on.
在我叫警察前 离开我的房子
Get off my property before I call the cops.
派克先生 听我说
Mr. Pike. Listen.
爸爸 他们只是想帮忙
Dad, they're just trying to help.
给我进去
Get in the house.
对不起 我说出了事实
Sorry. I told him the truth.
没关系 马特到底发生了什么
We had a plan, Matt. What happened to the plan?
听着现在是晚上12点呢
Look. It's 12 a.m.
他们马上就要来了
They are coming any minute now.
你必须带走你的家人 不然就太迟了
You need to get your family and go. Before it's too late.
是吗 你是指圣经上所谓的灾难
You mean, before the biblical swarm?
你想想究竟在那个经纪人身上 到底发生了什么事
Larry, what do you think really happened to that realtor?
还有那个燃气公司的雇员
And the gas-company guy.
你觉得这不奇怪吗
You don't think something weird's going on?
我不知道你们是谁 但我只知道你们疯了
I don't know who you are, but you're crazy.
你们再靠近我的孩子和家庭 我就得采取措施了
You come near my boy or my family again, we're gonna have a problem.
我也讨厌这样 可我们确实是有危险
We got a problem right now.
爸 他们是对的 我们有危险
Dad, they're right.We're in danger.
马特 现在进去
Matt, get inside! Now!
你为什么不听我的
No! Why won't you listen to me?
因为这很疯狂 这一点道理也没有
Because this is crazy! It doesn't make any sense!
听着 这片土地被诅咒了
Look, this land is cursed.
人们以前死在这里
People have died here.
你想拿你的家庭冒这个险吗
Are you gonna take that risk with your family?
等等
Wait.
你听到了吗
You hear it?
到底发生了什么事
What the hell?
现在该走了 拉里带上你妻子
It's time to go. Larry, get your wife. Yeah.
哦 伙计们
Guys?
哦 天啊
Oh, my God.
我从来没有遇到过
We'll never make it.
大家都进屋去
Everybody in the house.
都进去
Everybody in the house! Go!
周围还有其它人吗
Anyone else in the neighborhood?
没有 只有我们
No, it's just us.
亲爱的 发生什么拉
Honey, what's happening?
怎么这么吵 快报警
at's that noise? Call 91 1.
- 乔安妮 - 好的
- Joanie! - Okay.
我需要毛巾 我们要把这里锁起来
towels. The closet.
快 把门 窗壁和炉所有的都关上
We gotta lock this place up. Doors, windows, the fireplace, everything.
电话不通
The phones are dead.
他们一定是咬断了电话线
Must have chewed through the phone lines.
和电线
And the power lines.
也许我的手机能行
Maybe my cell…
没信号
No signal.
根本一点信号都没
You won't get one.
他们正在敲打着房子
They're blanketing the house.
那我们现在怎么办
So, what do we do now?
我们必须坚持下去
We try to outlast it.
希望太阳出来的时候诅咒能结束
Hopefully the curse will end at sunrise.
仅仅只是希望吗
"Hopefully"?
- 用杀虫剂 - 相信我
- Bug spray? - Trust me.
那是什么
What is that?
烟洞
The flue.
我想大家得上楼去
All right. I think everybody needs to get upstairs.
大家快上楼
Everybody upstairs! Now!
快 快 快
Go, go, go!
好的 Joanie
Hurry!
快
Come on!
走 快走
Go, go, go!
马特走 快点走
Go on, Matt!
快走
Go, go, go, go!
你进来了吗 快点
Hurry! Hurry, Matt!
快
Come on!
天啊 那是什么
Oh, God. What's that?
有东西在咬木头
Something's eating through the wood.
白蚁
Termites.
好的 大家都退后
All right. Everybody get back.
退后
Get back!
退后 退后
ck! Get back!
马特
Matt!
- 你说对了 - 是的
- ou got it? - Yeah.
快 快
Go, go, go!
废话
Crap.
怎么不说声再见
What, no goodbye?
来得刚好
Good timing.
再过一小时我们就走了
Another hour and we'd have been gone.
为什么
For good?
开发计划被取消了
Yeah. The development's on hold.
政府在调查你们发现的尸骨
while the government investigates the bones you found.
但我会确定没人会再住在这里
But l'm gonna make damn sure no one lives here again.
你看来并不生气啊
You don't seem too upset about it.
这是我一生中最重要的经济危机
Well, this has been the biggest financial disaster of my career…
但某种程度上来说 我真的不在乎
but somehow…l really don't care.
这是干吗
s this? I don't know.
我不知道 他们现在让我觉得恶心
They kind of weird me out now.
我也希望那样
Yeah, I should hope so.
我想找到老爸
I wanna find Dad.
我也是
Yeah, me too.
但我… 我想和他道歉
Yeah, but I just… I wanna apologize to him.
为了什么
For what?
为我对他说过的那些话
All the things I said to him.
他尽力做到最好了
He was just doing the best he could.
别担心 我们会找到他 那时你再道歉
ll, don't worry. We'll find him. And you'll apologize.
但那时可能5分钟后 你们又要吵开了
And then within five minutes, you'll be at each other's throats.
很可能
Yeah, probably.
- 让我们上路吧 - 好的
- Let's hit the road. - Let's.